Contact Details

+91 7775001644

gnpatil103@gmail.com

Education

 B.E. in Computer Science and Engineering from SKN Sinhgad college, Pandharpur, Solapur University, Maharashtra ()

Skills

- Hibernate
- Spring
- Spring Boot
- Microservices
- RESTful Web Services
- MySQL
- Agile Methodology
- Jenkins
- Docker
- Bitbucket
- Jira
- Maven
- Git
- Java 8
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Angular
- React Js
- MongoDB
- Node Js
- Kubernetes



Ganesh Patil

Professional Summary

Programmer Analyst with 4+ Years of Experience in developing applications using Hibernate, Spring, Spring Boot, Microservices, REST Webservices. Experienced in Agile methodology and working with tools like Jenkins, Docker, Bitbucket, Jira, and more.

Total Years of Experience

4 Years

Experience

1. Application Developer

Atos Syntel

07 March 2024 to 20th May 2024

- Not specified
- 2. Programmer Analyst

Cognizant

06 Jan 2022 to April 2023

- Not specified
- 3. Software Developer

Argus System

19 Aug 2019 to 31 Dec 2021

Not specified

Project Details

- 1. FedEx
- Logistic company dealing with various shipments

Technologies Used: Core Java, Spring, Spring Boot, Hibernate, MySQL, Junit, Mockito, Bitbucket, Jira, Agile, Docker, Maven, Postman, Log4j, Sonar Cube

Contact Details

+91 7775001644

gnpatil103@gmail.com

Education

 B.E. in Computer Science and Engineering from SKN Sinhgad college, Pandharpur, Solapur University, Maharashtra ()

Skills

- Hibernate
- Spring
- Spring Boot
- Microservices
- RESTful Web Services
- MySQL
- Agile Methodology
- Jenkins
- Docker
- Bitbucket
- Jira
- Maven
- Git
- Java 8
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Angular
- React Js
- MongoDB
- Node Js
- Kubernetes

2. RI - IES (Integrated Eligibility System)

 Health and insurance application for Rhode Island State Govt.

Technologies Used: Core Java, Spring, Spring Boot, Hibernate, MySQL, Junit, Mockito, Git, Jira, Agile, Docker, Maven, Postman, Log4j, SonarQube

3. HZ Harmonization

 Health Insurance project for Holland Zorg in Netherlands

Technologies Used: Core Java, Spring, Spring Boot, Hibernate, MySQL, Junit, Mockito, Bitbucket, Jira, Agile, Docker, Maven, Postman, Log4j, SonarQube